(Raj:)Really? So every other place
you've been,
(Raj:)you thought this was fine?
(Howard:)I know you're under a lot
of pressure,
(Howard:)so I'm gonna let that pass.
(sighs)
Sorry. You're right.
(Raj:)I'm so stressed.
(Raj:)But you know what,
(Raj:)whenever I walk
into that temple
(Raj:)I realize that whatever happens,
it's okay.
(Raj:)We're all part of
an immense pattern,
(Raj:)and though we can't understand
it, we can be happy to know
that it's-it's working its will
through us.
(Howard:)That's nice.
(chuckles)
(Raj:)Whether you call it God
or the universe or the self,
(Raj:)we're all interconnected,
and that's just a beautiful...
Son of a bitch!
That guy just dinged my car!
(gasps)
S-Seriously?
Y-You were
just gonna drive away?
(Raj:)Like my life
(Raj:)isn't hard enough right now.
(Raj:)A space probe
might be destroyed,
(Raj:)my parents are going
through an awful divorce,
(Raj:)the guy who cuts my dog's hair
just gave her bangs!
(Scene:)Raj.
(Raj:)You saw her. She looks like
Jim Carrey from Dumb and Dumber!